What was your first school like?
Not great, really.
The homework was too hard.
Did you have many friends there?
Only one or two, but the teachers were
nice.
What was your first school like?
Not great, really.
The homework was too hard.
Did you have many friends there?
Only one or two, but the teachers were
nice.
Shall we buy some oranges and bananas?
OK, if you want.
And the mangoes look nice too.
Shall we get one?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Hey, look at the strawberries.
Do you want some?
Oh yes, I love them.
Alright, let's get half a kilo.
Shall we buy some oranges and bananas?
OK, if you want.
And the mangoes look nice too.
Shall we get one?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Hey, look at the strawberries.
Do you want some?
Oh yes, I love them.
Alright, let's get half a kilo.
Let's meet for lunch.
I can do Saturday, next Tuesday or
Wednesday.
Ah, I can't do Saturday.
That's my brother's birthday.
What about next week then?
OK, Tuesday's fine.
Let's meet for lunch.
I can do Saturday, next Tuesday or
Wednesday.
Ah, I can do Saturday, next Tuesday or
I can't do Saturday, that's my brother's
birthday.
What about next week then?
OK, Tuesday's fine.
Is it true that Mark is a vegetarian?
Yes, now he mainly eats salads, fruit and
vegetables.
But he used to love eating meat.
He won't touch it, but he still eats a bit
of fish.
Is it true that Mark is a vegetarian?
Yes, now he mainly eats salads, fruit and
vegetables.
But he used to love eating meat.
He won't touch it, but he still eats a bit
of fish.
So where are the wedding cars?
The groom's already at the church and
we're going to be late.
I can't believe it.
Don't worry, they'll be here in a minute.
I'm sure they've just...
I can't help being worried.
It's not every day my daughter gets
married.
She's my daughter too.
Look, here they come now.
OK.
So where are the wedding cars?
The groom's already at the church and
we're going to be late.
I can't believe it.
Don't worry, they'll be here in a minute.
I'm sure they've just...
I can't help being worried.
It's not every day my daughter gets
married.
She's my daughter too.
Look, here they come now.
OK?
Hi Dad, I'm back.
Oh good.
So how was the swimming lesson then?
OK, but you know, 8 o'clock on a Saturday
morning.
It's so early.
But at least you have the rest of the day
to do other things, like go to town with
your friends and shop for new clothes.
Oh Dad.
Anyway, how was it?
Well, there were three of us in the class.
The teacher told us to swim really fast
and gave a t-shirt to the winner of the
race.
And was it fun?
Yeah, actually.
I really like trying to win.
And I'm good, you know.
Yes, I know.
Your teacher told me.
I need a new swimming costume too.
Why?
What's wrong with the one you have?
It's a bit too small for me.
OK, so we'll go to the shops tomorrow and
get you a new one.
Now, where's your towel?
Oh, sorry Dad.
I think I left it in the changing room at
the pool.
Oh Susan, you're hopeless.
Hi Dad, I'm back.
Oh good.
So how was the swimming lesson then?
OK, but you know, 8 o'clock on a Saturday
morning.
It's so early.
But at least you have the rest of the day
to do other things like go to town with
your friends and shop for new clothes.
Oh Dad.
Anyway, how was it?
Well, there were three of us in the class.
The teacher told us to swim really fast
and gave a t-shirt to the winner of the
race.
And was it fun?
Yeah, actually.
I really like trying to win.
And I'm good, you know.
Yes, I know.
Your teacher told me.
I need a new swimming costume too.
Why?
What's wrong with the one you have?
It's a bit too small for me.
OK, so we'll go to the shops tomorrow and
get you a new one.
Now, where's your towel?
Oh, sorry Dad.
I think I left it in the changing room at
the pool.
Oh Susan, you're hopeless.
Dad, can you give me a lift into town
tomorrow?
Yeah, I expect so.
Do you want to do some clothes shopping or
something?
No, I've got to get some earrings.
What more?
You've got so many.
No Dad, they're for Jenny.
It's her birthday on Friday.
I see.
OK.
Where do you want to get them from?
That little place opposite the bookshop.
You know, next to the chemist's.
Oh yes, I know.
Oh wait a minute.
I'm back late tomorrow.
I've got a meeting at three so I'll get
the 4.15 train.
So I should be back here at five.
But everything will be shut by then.
No, that's OK.
They stay open till six on Thursdays.
Dad?
I've got a meeting at three so I'll get
the 4.15 train.
So I should be back here at five.
But everything will be shut by then.
No, I've got to get some clothes shopping.
Oh, I've got to get some earrings.
What more?
You've got so many.
No Dad, they're for Jenny.
It's her birthday on Friday.
I see.
OK.
Where do you want to get them from?
That little place opposite the bookshop.
You know, next to the chemist's.
Oh yes, I know.
Oh wait a minute.
I'm back late tomorrow.
I've got a meeting at three so I'll get
the 4.15 train.
No, that's OK.
They stay open till six on Thursdays.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Please.
I'm looking for a hotel.
But I don't have much money to spend.
There are no hotels in this small village,
I'm afraid.
Just people's houses.
In the next town, there's a big hotel on
the beach, but that's very expensive.
And there are some new villas there too,
overlooking the sea.
Are you travelling alone?
No.
I'm with a friend.
She's just coming.
All we need is a room for a few days.
We can find you a room, no problem.
My job is to help tourists.
Look, that's my office over there.
OK.
So could you just tell me how much a room
costs?
Not too much.
About 20 euros.
What?
Per person?
No, for the room.
And if you stay for a week, it's even
cheaper.
Maybe 120.
Oh, that sounds OK.
Have you got anything near the beach?
Yes.
I can find you something, no problem.
and then I can show you some places and
see if we can find you something that you
like.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Please.
I'm looking for a hotel, but I don't have
much money to spend.
There are no hotels in this small village,
I'm afraid.
Just people's houses.
In the next town, there's a big hotel on
the beach, but that's very expensive.
And there are some new villas there too,
overlooking the sea.
Are you travelling alone?
No.
I'm with a friend.
She's just coming.
All we need is a room for a few days.
We can find you a room, no problem.
My job is to help tourists.
Look, that's my office over there.
OK.
So, could you just tell me how much a room
costs?
Not too much.
About 20 euros.
What?
Per person?
No, for the room.
And if you stay for a week, it's even
cheaper.
Maybe 120.
Oh, that sounds OK.
Have you got anything near the beach?
Yes.
I can find you something, no problem.
Look, we can wait for your friend.
And then I can show you some places.
And see if we can find you something that
you like.
Can I return these ones, please?
Yes, certainly.
Thank you.
Was there anything else?
Well, I ordered a book last week.
Can you check if it's arrived yet?
Sure.
Can I have your library card, please?
I just have to find your details on the
computer.
Sorry.
The computer's being a bit slow.
That's all right.
No, sorry.
It's not here yet.
Oh.
Also, do you have anything happening for
children this week?
Yes.
We have story time at 2pm this Friday.
It's for the under fives.
How much does it cost?
Oh, it's free for members.
And while that's on, mums and dads can
look around our exhibition of local
history.
That's great.
We'll come back on Friday then.
Can I return these ones, please?
Yes, certainly.
Thank you.
Was there anything else?
Well, I ordered a book last week.
Can you check if it's arrived yet?
Sure.
Can I have your library card, please?
I just have to find your details on the
computer.
Sorry.
The computer's being a bit slow.
That's all right.
No, sorry.
It's not here yet.
Oh.
Also, do you have anything happening for
children this week?
Yes.
We have story time at 2pm this Friday.
It's for the under fives.
How much does it cost?
Oh, it's free for members.
And while that's on, mums and dads can
look around our exhibition of local
history.
That's great.
We'll come back on Friday then.
Good afternoon.
May I help you, madam?
Yes, please.
I'd like to go on holiday next week.
To the sunshine.
No problem.
Any country in mind?
Somewhere nice and warm, that's all.
How about this hotel in Egypt?
The weather's lovely right now.
That looks great, but a little expensive
for me, I think.
Hmm.
How about this apartment in Italy?
Tuscany.
That looks wonderful.
Can I go next week?
I'm sorry.
It's not available for another month.
Never mind.
Anything in Spain or Greece?
There's this small hotel in Spain.
What do you think?
That looks great.
It's right on the beach.
And you can go next week.
Perfect.
And not too expensive.
No.
Then I'll take it.
Thanks so much for your help.
Good afternoon.
May I help you, madam?
Yes, please.
I'd like to go on holiday next week.
To the sunshine.
No problem.
Any country in mind?
Somewhere nice and warm, that's all.
How about this hotel in Egypt?
The weather's lovely right now.
That looks great, but a little expensive
for me, I think.
Hmm.
How about this apartment in Italy?
Tuscany.
That looks wonderful.
Can I go next week?
I'm sorry.
It's not available for another month.
Never mind.
Anything in Spain or Greece?
There's this small hotel in Spain.
What do you think?
That looks great.
It's right on the beach.
And you can go next week.
Perfect.
And not too expensive.
No.
Then I'll take it.
Thanks so much for your help.
The first room is the kitchen.
It's quite small, but it has everything
you need.
There's a cooker and a small fridge.
And from the window you can see the
garden.
The sitting room is down here too.
This is a much bigger room and very light
and comfortable.
Just through that door there is a
downstairs bathroom.
Outside the garden is very large.
And as you can hear, the area is very
peaceful.
There's no traffic noise.
Let's go upstairs.
Here you've got four bedrooms.
They're nice and big and two of them have
got bathrooms.
The first room is the kitchen.
It's quite small, but it has everything
you need.
There's a cooker and a small fridge.
And from the window you can see the
garden.
The sitting room is down here too.
This is a much bigger room and very light
and comfortable.
Just through that door there is a
downstairs bathroom.
Outside the garden is very large.
And as you can hear, the area is very
peaceful.
There's no traffic noise.
Let's go upstairs.
Here you've got four bedrooms.
They're nice and big and two of them have
got bathrooms.
I'm a photographer.
I do a lot of work at home.
I usually get up at 6 o'clock and go for a
run.
When I get home, I have a shower and then
I eat breakfast.
At half past eight, my children go to
school and my wife leaves for work.
At 9 o'clock, I sit down at my computer
and start my work.
First, I read and send emails.
I advertise my photos on my website.
I make lots of people buy them from there.
At about 10.30, I take my camera and go
for a walk.
I live in the country and there are a lot
of beautiful places to photograph.
I sometimes go for meetings in London.
On those days, I leave home early in the
morning.
I enjoy my job very much and I think I
always will.
I'm a photographer.
I do a lot of work at home.
I usually get up at 6 o'clock and go for a
run.
When I get home, I have a shower and then
I eat breakfast.
At half past eight, my children go to
school and my wife leaves for work.
At 9 o'clock, I sit down at my computer
and start my work.
First, I read and send emails.
I advertise my photos on my website and
lots of people buy them from there.
At about 10.30, I take my camera and go
for a walk.
I live in the country and there are a lot
of beautiful places to photograph.
I sometimes go for meetings in London.
On those days, I leave home early in the
morning.
I enjoy my job very much and I think I
always will.
This is Petra Harris with a programme
announcement.
On Wednesday evening, we have a special
programme from Africa.
Brian Williams is a reporter and he lived
there with a group of elephants for six
months.
This is his story.
There are some sad moments.
For example, when Jemma, a baby elephant,
dies.
But there are happy moments too.
We see the elephants in the water playing
like children.
It wasn't easy for Brian because the sun
was very strong and sometimes he didn't
have water.
He had a lot of help from the African
people.
One man, Charlie, was with him all the
time and is now his best friend.
So don't miss this programme.
Everyone who loves animals will enjoy it.
Wednesday evening, 8.30 on Channel 6.
This is Petra Harris with a programme
announcement.
On Wednesday evening, we have a special
programme from Africa.
Brian Williams is a reporter and he lived
there with a group of elephants for six
months.
This is his story.
There are some sad moments.
For example, when Jemma, a baby elephant,
dies.
But there are happy moments too.
We see the elephants in the water playing
like children.
It wasn't easy for Brian because the sun
was very strong and sometimes he didn't
have water.
He had a lot of help from the African
people.
One man, Charlie, was with him all the
time and is now his best friend.
So don't miss this programme.
Everyone who loves animals will enjoy it.
Wednesday evening, 8.30 on Channel 6.
Are you happy in your job?
Or would you like a change?
Perhaps you need new skills.
At Preston College, you can study many
different subjects to help you find a new
job.
On Monday and Wednesday evenings, we have
courses in business skills.
Or why not learn another language?
On Saturday morning, you can study French.
And on Saturday evening, you can learn
Spanish or German.
Do you need better computer skills?
There's a course on Saturday afternoons.
And if you just need keyboard typing
skills, come to our beginners class on
Monday mornings.
So, think about the future and come along
to Preston College.
Are you happy in your job?
Or would you like a change?
Perhaps you need new skills.
At Preston College, you can study many
different subjects to help you find a new
job.
On Monday and Wednesday evenings, we have
courses in business skills.
Or why not learn another language?
On Saturday morning, you can study French.
And on Saturday evening, you can learn
Spanish or German.
Or why not learn another language?
Do you need better computer skills?
There's a course on Saturday afternoons.
And if you just need keyboard typing
skills, come to our beginners class on
Monday mornings.
So, think about the future and come along
to Preston College.
Our brand new sports centre on Chapel Road
opens soon.
It opens to the public on Wednesday 10th
May.
We'd like to invite you to come and visit
us on Monday 8th to meet the staff and get
your early membership.
Also on Monday, you can walk around the
centre and see the facilities.
We're open any time after 9 in the
morning.
We have a gym, tennis courts and a pool
for our members.
All of those will be open every day until
9pm, apart from Fridays when we're closed
at 6.
Bring your children along too.
They'll love it here after a long day at
school.
Our brand new sports centre on Chapel Road
opens soon.
It opens to the public on Wednesday 10th
May.
We'd like to invite you to come and visit
us on Monday 8th to meet the staff and get
your early membership.
We'd like to invite you to come and visit
us on Monday 8th to meet the staff and get
your early membership.
We're open any time after 9 in the
morning.
We have a gym, tennis courts and a pool
for our members.
All of those will be open every day until
9pm, apart from Fridays when we're closed
at 6.
Bring your children along too.
They'll love it here after a long day at
school.